{
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "Explore our website's jungle for an immersive adventure. Now, enter 'START' to begin.",
        "answer": "START"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "You are new to the jungle, Find the place where newcomers go to introduce themselves and get WELCOME party.",
        "answer": "I am new here!"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Response to your request at HEADERS party has hidden information. Peek at them closely to uncover a secret.",
        "answer": "SHH! Some one found us"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "You've stored something important. Check where you keep your snacks.",
        "answer": "Yummy, food!"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "The jungle's blueprint holds secrets. Investigate its layout carefully.",
        "answer": "Nice, You explored the DOM!!"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "There's something crawling around in here. How can you stop it?",
        "answer": "Dangerous, Web Crawler"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "How did you ask to come here? Figure out the way you requested entry.",
        "answer": "GET"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Something sweet is waiting for you. Check where treats are stored.",
        "answer": "Eat until you are full!"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "You're almost out. Look for the path that leads you to ESCAPE.",
        "answer": "Let's escape!"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Well done, you survived!",
        "answer": ""
      }
    ]
  }
  